SEN. SCHMITT: YEAH, AND HIS CENTRAL PLANK OF HIS TEAM, OF HIS CAMPAIGN
SEN. SCHMITT: YEAH, AND HIS CENTRAL PLANK OF HIS TEAM, OF HIS CAMPAIGN WAS
SEN. SCHMITT: YEAH, AND HIS CENTRAL PLANK OF HIS TEAM, OF HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT
SEN. SCHMITT: YEAH, AND HIS CENTRAL PLANK OF HIS TEAM, OF HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE
SEN. SCHMITT: YEAH, AND HIS CENTRAL PLANK OF HIS TEAM, OF HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD
CENTRAL PLANK OF HIS TEAM, OF HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD
CENTRAL PLANK OF HIS TEAM, OF HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED
CENTRAL PLANK OF HIS TEAM, OF HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED PRESIDENT
CENTRAL PLANK OF HIS TEAM, OF HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED
HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME
HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I
HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE
HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT,
HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I
HIS CAMPAIGN WAS THAT HE HAD PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO
PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO
PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO WANT
PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO WANT TO
PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO WANT TO ASK
PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO WANT TO ASK YOU
PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT
PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A
PROSECUTED PRESIDENT TRUMP. LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE
LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE
LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE OF
LIMITED TIME I HAVE LEFT, I DO WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE OF THINGS.
WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE OF THINGS.
WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE OF THINGS. DID
WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE OF THINGS. DID YOU
WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE OF THINGS. DID YOU GO
WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE OF THINGS. DID YOU GO TO
WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE OF THINGS. DID YOU GO TO AN
WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE OF THINGS. DID YOU GO TO AN NBA
WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT A COUPLE OF THINGS. DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME
OF THINGS. DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME
OF THINGS. DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME BETWEEN
OF THINGS. DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME BETWEEN THE
OF THINGS. DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME BETWEEN THE GOLDEN
OF THINGS. DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE
DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE
DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS
DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS AND
DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS AND THE
DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA
DID YOU GO TO AN NBA GAME BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS
BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS
BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON
BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON FEBRUARY
BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3,
BETWEEN THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024?
WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024?
WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR.
WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH:
WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: I'M
WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY,
WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN
WARRIORS AND THE ATLANTA HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU
ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU
ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY
ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY THAT
ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY THAT AGAIN?
MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY THAT AGAIN?
MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN.
MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT:
MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID
MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU
MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO
MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO
MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY, CAN YOU SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A
SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A
SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA
SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME
SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME BETWEEN
SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME BETWEEN THE
SAY THAT AGAIN? SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS
SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS
SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND
SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS
SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON
SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY
SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3,
SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU GO TO A NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024?
NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024?
NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR.
NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH:
NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: WHAT
NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: WHAT CITY
NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: WHAT CITY WOULD
NBA GAME BETWEEN THE WARRIORS AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: WHAT CITY WOULD THAT
AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: WHAT CITY WOULD THAT
AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: WHAT CITY WOULD THAT BE
AND HAWKS ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? MR. SMITH: WHAT CITY WOULD THAT BE IN?
MR. SMITH: WHAT CITY WOULD THAT BE IN?
MR. SMITH: WHAT CITY WOULD THAT BE IN? SEN.
MR. SMITH: WHAT CITY WOULD THAT BE IN? SEN. SCHMITT:
MR. SMITH: WHAT CITY WOULD THAT BE IN? SEN. SCHMITT: ATLANTA.
BE IN? SEN. SCHMITT: ATLANTA.
BE IN? SEN. SCHMITT: ATLANTA. MR.
BE IN? SEN. SCHMITT: ATLANTA. MR. SMITH:
BE IN? SEN. SCHMITT: ATLANTA. MR. SMITH: NO.
SEN. SCHMITT: ATLANTA. MR. SMITH: NO.
SEN. SCHMITT: ATLANTA. MR. SMITH: NO. SEN.
SEN. SCHMITT: ATLANTA. MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT:
SEN. SCHMITT: ATLANTA. MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR
SEN. SCHMITT: ATLANTA. MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID NOT
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID NOT GO
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS
SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS
SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME,
SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, IS
SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, IS THAT
SEN. SCHMITT: YOUR TESTIMONY TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, IS THAT CORRECT?
TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, IS THAT CORRECT?
TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, IS THAT CORRECT? MR.
TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, IS THAT CORRECT? MR. SMITH:
TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, IS THAT CORRECT? MR. SMITH: I
TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, IS THAT CORRECT? MR. SMITH: I HAVE
TODAY YOU DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, IS THAT CORRECT? MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO
GAME, IS THAT CORRECT? MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO
GAME, IS THAT CORRECT? MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION
GAME, IS THAT CORRECT? MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION OF
GAME, IS THAT CORRECT? MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION OF THAT.
MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION OF THAT.
MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN.
MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN. SCHMITT:
MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN. SCHMITT: IS
MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT
MR. SMITH: I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR
RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR
RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY
RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY YOU
RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY YOU WERE
RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT
RECOLLECTION OF THAT. SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN
SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN
SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA
SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON
SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY
SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3,
SEN. SCHMITT: IS IT YOUR TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024?
TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024?
TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? LET
TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? LET ME
TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? LET ME JUST
TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? LET ME JUST GIVE
TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? LET ME JUST GIVE YOU
TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A
TESTIMONY YOU WERE NOT IN ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE
ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE
ATLANTA ON FEBRUARY 3, 2024? LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE CONTEXT.
LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE CONTEXT.
LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE CONTEXT. THE
LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE CONTEXT. THE DAY
LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE
LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE
LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS
LET ME JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS CAME
CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS CAME
CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS CAME CLEAR
CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS CAME CLEAR WITH
CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS CAME CLEAR WITH HER
CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS CAME CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR
CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS CAME CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH
CONTEXT. THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS CAME CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH THE
THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS CAME CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH THE
THE DAY BEFORE FANNIE LEWIS CAME CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH THE PROSECUTOR.
CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH THE PROSECUTOR.
CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH THE PROSECUTOR. YOU
CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH THE PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW
CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH THE PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW THE
CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH THE PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR
CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH THE PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT
CLEAR WITH HER AFFAIR WITH THE PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS
PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS
PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO
PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING
PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING TO
PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING TO GET
PROSECUTOR. YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING TO GET TRUMP.
YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING TO GET TRUMP.
YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING TO GET TRUMP. THE
YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING TO GET TRUMP. THE NEXT
YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING TO GET TRUMP. THE NEXT DAY,
YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING TO GET TRUMP. THE NEXT DAY, WERE
YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING TO GET TRUMP. THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU
YOU KNOW THE PROSECUTOR THAT WAS ALSO TRYING TO GET TRUMP. THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN
ALSO TRYING TO GET TRUMP. THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN
ALSO TRYING TO GET TRUMP. THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN ATLANTA?
THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN ATLANTA?
THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN ATLANTA? MR.
THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN ATLANTA? MR. SMITH:
THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I
THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO
THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT
THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE
THE NEXT DAY, WERE YOU IN ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO.
ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO.
ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN.
ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT:
ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID
ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU
ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER
ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO
ATLANTA? MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO TO
MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO TO
MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO TO ATLANTA
MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO TO ATLANTA DURING
MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO TO ATLANTA DURING YOUR
MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO TO ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME
MR. SMITH: I DO NOT BELIEVE SO. SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO TO ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS
SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO TO ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS
SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO TO ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL
SEN. SCHMITT: DID YOU EVER GO TO ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL?
ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL?
ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR.
ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH:
ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: I
ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: I REALLY
ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T
ATLANTA DURING YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T THINK
SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T THINK
SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T THINK SO.
MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T THINK SO.
MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T THINK SO. IT'S
MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T THINK SO. IT'S POSSIBLE
MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T THINK SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I
MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T THINK SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW
MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T THINK SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH
MR. SMITH: I REALLY DON'T THINK SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE
SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE
SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA
SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT
SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON
SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE
SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY
SO. IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO
IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO
IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA,
IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT
IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT I
IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT I DO
IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT I DO NOT
IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT I DO NOT HAVE
IT'S POSSIBLE I FLEW THROUGH THE ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT I DO NOT HAVE A
ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT I DO NOT HAVE A
ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT I DO NOT HAVE A RECOLLECTION
ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT I DO NOT HAVE A RECOLLECTION OF
ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT I DO NOT HAVE A RECOLLECTION OF GOING
ATLANTA AIRPORT ON THE WAY TO FLORIDA, BUT I DO NOT HAVE A RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO
FLORIDA, BUT I DO NOT HAVE A RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO
FLORIDA, BUT I DO NOT HAVE A RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO ATLANTA.
RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO ATLANTA.
RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO ATLANTA. I
RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY
RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID
RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT
RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO
RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO
RECOLLECTION OF GOING TO ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A
ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A
ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS
ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME,
ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M
ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE
ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF
ATLANTA. I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT.
I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT.
I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN.
I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME
I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET:
I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID
I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU
I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER
I DEFINITELY DID NOT GO TO A HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET
HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET
HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN
HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE
HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE OR
HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE OR FANI
HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS
HAWKS GAME, I'M SURE OF THAT. SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN
SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN
SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN YOUR
SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN YOUR TIME
SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN YOUR TIME AS
SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL
SEN. SOME YET: DID YOU EVER MEET NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL?
NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL?
NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR.
NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH:
NATHAN WADE OR FANI LEWIS IN YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: NO.
YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: NO.
YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: NO. SEN.
YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT:
YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT
YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD
YOUR TIME AS SPECIAL COUNSEL? MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF
MR. SMITH: NO. SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT
SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT
SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT
SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU
SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE
SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT
SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT A
SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS
SEN. SCHMITT: WHAT WOULD YOU TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME
TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME
TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME THE
TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME THE DAY
TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME THE DAY AFTER
TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME THE DAY AFTER WILLIS
TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND
TEAM IF I HAD A SERIES OF TEXT THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE
THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE
THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED
THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED THEIR
THAT YOU WERE AT A HAWKS GAME THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR?
THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR?
THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR? I
THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR? I DON'T
THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR? I DON'T THINK
THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR? I DON'T THINK YOU
THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR? I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW
THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR? I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE
THE DAY AFTER WILLIS AND WADE ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR? I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE
ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR? I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE
ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR? I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE THIS
ANNOUNCED THEIR AFFAIR? I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE THIS STUFF.
I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE THIS STUFF.
I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE THIS STUFF. I'LL
I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE
I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU
I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A
I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND
I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW WE HAVE THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO
THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO
THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO PROCESS
THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO PROCESS IT
THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO PROCESS IT SO
THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO PROCESS IT SO YOU
THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO PROCESS IT SO YOU UP
THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T
THIS STUFF. I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER
I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER
I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER JUROR
I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND TO PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER JUROR YOURSELF.
PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER JUROR YOURSELF.
PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER JUROR YOURSELF. MR.
PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER JUROR YOURSELF. MR. SMITH:
PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER JUROR YOURSELF. MR. SMITH: YOU
PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER JUROR YOURSELF. MR. SMITH: YOU JUST
PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER JUROR YOURSELF. MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK
PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER JUROR YOURSELF. MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK IT
PROCESS IT SO YOU UP DON'T PER JUROR YOURSELF. MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK IT DOWN
JUROR YOURSELF. MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK IT DOWN
JUROR YOURSELF. MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK IT DOWN REALLY
JUROR YOURSELF. MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK IT DOWN REALLY QUICK.
MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK IT DOWN REALLY QUICK.
MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK IT DOWN REALLY QUICK. IF
MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK IT DOWN REALLY QUICK. IF I
MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK IT DOWN REALLY QUICK. IF I COULD
MR. SMITH: YOU JUST TOOK IT DOWN REALLY QUICK. IF I COULD LOOK